

## **CODING LANGUAGES**

C, C++ HTML CSS JavaScript PHP SQL

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

#### CONTACT

P: 080-919-1449 E: au.garh1999@gmail.com A: 417 Bang Yi Ruea, Thon Buri, Bangkok 10600

#### **PORTFOLIO**



## SOCIAL

fb.me/au.garh

@au.garh

@au\_garh

# NUTHAWUT LEELAVISEDSAK

## BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

#### **ABOUT**

I have always been interested in computers and studied them since childhood. Then I had the intention of becoming a hardware expert. I'm starting to have an interest in software as well. Therefore, I chose to study computer science at Bansomdetchaopraya Rajabhat University. Programming is currently one of my best subjects in university.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Jps Creative Innovation Co., Ltd. | Jan 2020 - Apr 2021

- Website designing, building, and maintaining.
- Directing and performing Website updates.
- Managing the company's inventory system.

## **EVENT STAFF**

Commart Thailand | Aug 2020 - Mar 2021

- Sales asisstance
- Build A PC

## PART-TIME EMPLOYEE

7-11 | Aug 2020 - Mar 2021

- Cashier
- Barista
- Managing inventory

## EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Bansomdetchaopraya Rajabhat University | 2018 - NOW GPA 3.71

HIGH SCHOOL - MIDDLE SCHOOL

Debsirin School | 2012 - 2017 GPA 3.64

ELEMENTARY SCHOOL GRADE 4 - GRADE 6

Mahaweeranuwat School | 2009 - 2011

KINDERGARTEN - ELEMENTARY SCHOOL GRADE 1 - GRADE 3

kantatararam School | 2004 - 2008